tollywoodblog.in 2012-12-23

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer Telugu Cinema News Updates Website

##  [Privacy Policy and Disclaimer](http://www.tollywoodblog.in/2008/09/privacy-policy-and-disclaimer.html)

Privacy Policy 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

Sites like Google AdSense, Google Analytics, FeedBurner, Flickr or [other third-party services](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may place and read cookies or use web beacons to collect non-personal information. These services use the data to track conversions, to show statistics about this site or to improve their features.

The ads from this site are served by Google AdSense, a third-party service that shows contextually-targeted ads, placement-targeted ads and interested-based ads. Google uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) to serve ads based on the sites you have recently visited. You can go to the [Google Ads Preferences page](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie.

Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns please contact me at  . This privacy policy updated December 2010

Disclaimer

Some images contained in [tollywoodblog.in](http://tollywoodblog.in/) have been obtained from various internet sources. The copyright of these pictures belongs to their original publisher / photographer. Please let us know at  if any Copyright Violation occurs and we will remove them right away. 

If by anyhow any of the content is offensive to you, please, contact us asking for the removal. If you own copyrights over any of them and do not agree with it being shown here, please send us an email with ownership proof and we will remove it. email us at -
